[
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89]?",
      "correctAnswer": "85",
      "options": [
        "84",
        "85",
        "86",
        "87"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90]?",
      "correctAnswer": "86",
      "options": [
        "85",
        "86",
        "87",
        "88"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91]?",
      "correctAnswer": "87",
      "options": [
        "86",
        "87",
        "88",
        "89"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92]?",
      "correctAnswer": "88",
      "options": [
        "87",
        "88",
        "89",
        "90"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93]?",
      "correctAnswer": "89",
      "options": [
        "88",
        "89",
        "90",
        "91"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94]?",
      "correctAnswer": "90",
      "options": [
        "89",
        "90",
        "91",
        "92"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95]?",
      "correctAnswer": "91",
      "options": [
        "90",
        "91",
        "92",
        "93"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96]?",
      "correctAnswer": "92",
      "options": [
        "91",
        "92",
        "93",
        "94"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97]?",
      "correctAnswer": "93",
      "options": [
        "92",
        "93",
        "94",
        "95"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98]?",
      "correctAnswer": "94",
      "options": [
        "93",
        "94",
        "95",
        "96"
      ]
    }
]